Oh, why do these kinds of things always happen to us?
为什么这种事总是发生在我们身上啊？
What are we going to do?
我们现在该怎么办啊？
What we always do!
干我们的老本行啊！
Save the day!
拯救大家！
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy!
天哪，天哪，天哪！
This is gonna be so much fun!
这一定会非常好玩的！
Oh! I only wish we had time to make superhero capes!
我真希望我们能抽点儿时间去做几件超级英雄披风！
Oh, me too!
加我一个！
Enough about our wardrobe!
别再聊那些穿的东西了！
We've got to stop Gloriosa from trapping everybody in here!
我们还得阻止嘉兰把大家困在营地里呢！
Um, hi
呃，嗨
Do you think you can give us a hand–
你们能否帮我们一把…
Um, er, paw? We could really use a way out
呃，一爪？我们真的很需要一条能出去的路
This isn't working!
没有用！
Her magic is too strong!
她的魔法太强大了！
Nice work, Spike!
干得好，斯派克！
Twilight, you have to use your magic!
暮光，你必须使用你的魔法！
I don't think I can lift something that big
我不觉得我能搬得动这么大的东西
It's our only chance of getting out of here
这是我们能帮助朋友们
and helping our friends!
并逃离这里的唯一可能啊！
Why are you fighting me?
为何你们都要跟我作对？
I'm doing this to save our camp!
我可是在拯救我们营地啊！
I'm doing this for you!
我可是为了你们好！
Gloriosa, let's just think about this for a moment, shall we?
嘉兰，我们来稍微讨论下这事如何？
I mean, I think Camp Everfree is absolutely delightful
我是说，森灵营地的确非常棒
but I just don't know that if I'm quite ready to give up my weekly trips to the spa.
但我不知道我是否准备好放弃享受我每周一次的水疗了
To the spa
享受水疗？
TO THE SPA?!
享受水疗？！
Gloriosa, this isn't the way!
嘉兰，没必要这样！
I appreciate your concern, Timber
我很感谢你的关心，云杉
BUT I GOT THIS!
但是我会搞定的！
No, you don't!
不，你没有！
Twilight, do you think you can use your magic?
暮光，你能使用你的魔法吗？
I don't wanna use too much
我不想使用过度
Midnight Sparkle could take over
午夜闪闪可能会控制我
Twilight, our friends are in there!
暮光，我们的朋友可都在里面啊！
Okay
好吧
Please, Gloriosa
嘉兰，拜托
What you're doing is crazy
你的所作所为简直太疯狂了
You have to listen to me!
你一定得听我说！
That isn't Gloriosa
那不是嘉兰
Twilight!
暮光！
Sunset!
余晖！
You're okay!
没事吧你们！
That isn't your sister
那不是你姐姐
It's someone who's been consumed by Equestrian magic.
那只是个被小马国魔法吞噬的人而已
Whoever you are, you have to let my sister go!
不管你是谁，快把我姐姐还回来！
Please, Gloriosa, come back!
拜托，嘉兰，快点回来！
I need you!
我需要你！
Gloriosa!
嘉兰！
Rarity!
瑞瑞！
I can't keep this up forever!
我没办法永远挡住这些荆棘！
It's up to you
看你的了
You can use your magic to pull the brambles apart!
你可以用你的魔法扯断这些荆棘！
No. There's too many of them
不行，太多了
It would take too much magic. I can't!
我做不到！这会消耗太多魔法了！
It's the only way!
这是唯一的办法了！
You have to embrace the magic inside you!
你得接纳你的魔法
What if she takes over?
万一她控制了我呢？
What if instead of saving everyone
万一我变成了午夜闪闪
I turn into Midnight Sparkle and only make things worse?
不仅没能救到我们反而让事情变得雪上加霜了呢？
That won't happen!
那不会发生的！
We won't let it
我们不会让它发生的
Come on, Twilight!
来吧，暮光！
You have to be stronger than she is!
你得要比她更强大！
You will never control me! I will always be a part of you!
你永远无法掌控我！我永远是你的一部分！
Nooo!
不要！
Twilight, listen to me! You are in charge!
暮光，听我说！你可以控制住的！
You are a light, darling! A force for good!
你是一道光，亲爱的！你是正义的力量
Yeah! You can kick the darkness's butt!
对！你能赶走黑暗势力的！
We're here for you, Twilight!
我们支持你，暮光！
And we'll be here no matter what!
而且我们无论如何都会在你身边
We believe in you!
我们相信你！
You are not Midnight Sparkle!
你不是午夜闪闪！
No! I am Twilight Sparkle!
没错！我是暮光闪闪！
And the magic I carry inside me is... the Magic of Friendship!
而且我心中的魔法就是友谊魔法！
No! Stop!
不！住手！
Gloriosa?
嘉兰？
What... What happened?
发…发生了什么事？
It's okay
没事了
It's gonna be okay
已经没事了
You did it!
你做到了！
Oh, nice bling
喔，光泽不错
What... What are these?
这些...东西到底是啥？
I'm not sure
我不知道
But clearly we have some kind of connection to them
但显然的我们跟这些东西有着某种联系
I almost don't care what they are
我才不管这些东西是什么呢
They are gorgeous!
它们看起来超漂亮！
And will totally go with the other collection I was working on for the camp fashion show!
和我为了营地时装秀而做出的其他作品很搭
That's probably cancelled, isn't it?
不过时装秀应该已经被取消了，对吧？
I am so sorry
我真的很抱歉
I only wanted this to be the best week Camp Everfree has ever had
我只是想要让大家有个史上最棒的露营周
Then instead I've made it the worst
结果我却搞砸了一切
Maybe it's for the best that I'm losing the camp to Filthy Rich
或许让臭钱接手营地才是最好的选择
No, it's not
不，并不是
This camp has meant so much to so many people
这营地对很多人来说都很重要
my sister and me included
包括了我和我的妹妹
Why do you think we wanted our students to come here?
不然你认为我们为什么会选择带我们的学生来到这里
We can't let Filthy Rich take this place away!
我们不能让臭钱夺走这座营地！
If camp meant so much to you two
如果这营地对你们姐弟俩很重要
maybe it meant as much to the other campers who came here in years past
或许也对历年以来在这里露营的其他营员们一样重要
And maybe we can get them to help save it!
也许我们能让他们帮忙一起来拯救营地！
Oh! Like a fundraiser?
哦，像是办场募捐活动？
Or a ball?!
或是办场舞会？
Our band could play!
我们乐队可以表演！
I can help writing a new song just for the occasion!
我可以帮忙专门写首新歌！
Those are all good ideas, but where would we hold it?
这些的确都是好主意，但我们该在哪里举办？
We can hold it in the crystal cave!
我们可以办在水晶洞穴里！
A Crystal Ball! I'm on it!
一场水晶舞会！我这就去办！
I admire everyone's enthusiasm
我很感谢大家的热情相助
Really, I do
真的
But I-I just don't know how we're going to plan a ball by tomorrow
但我-我不知道要怎么才能赶在明天前筹备好一场舞会
and invite everyone
并邀请大家都来参加
We got this!
我们会搞定的！